//for the future
var cheatsheet = [
    {
        question:"What HTML tag do you use for JavaScript?",
        choices:["<div>","<a>","<script>","<p>"],
        correctChoice: "<script>"
    },
    {
        question:"what section do you put the JavaScript link",
        choices:["<html>","<main>","<body> and <head>","<body> and <html>"],
        correctChoice: "<body> and <head>"
    },
    {
        question:"Whats JavaScripts main purpose?",
        choices:["Sets up the framework of a webpage","Makes web pages interactive", "linking pictures to a webpage", "styling a webpage"],
        correctChoice: "Makes web pages interactive"
    },
    {
        question:"are JavaScript variables case sensitive?",
        choices:["sometimes","no","yes"],
        correctChoice: "yes"
    },
    {
        question:"which one of these is not a Javascript operator?",
        choices:["%","===","!==","+"],
        correctChoice: "%"
    },
    {
        question:"What type of data does the variable equal in testVariable = true;?",
        choices:["String","Boolean", "Number", "Array"],
        correctChoice: "Boolean"
    },
    {
        question:"A good tool to use when debugging JavaScript is",
        choices:["code .","console.log", "alt + F4", "getCode.error"],
        correctChoice: "console.log"
    },
    {
        question:"Who created JavaScript",
        choices:["James Gosling","Bill Gates", "Brendan Eich", "Larry Page"],
        correctChoice: "Brendan Eich"
    },
    {
        question:"What year was JavaScript created?",
        choices:["2002","1988", "1997", "1995"],
        correctChoice: "1995"
    },
    {
        question:"How long did it take to build JavaSctipy",
        choices:["10 days","1 year", "8 months", "24 days"],
        correctChoice: "10 days"
    },
]